

IRYNA SKARAIEVA

Front-End Developer

I'm a Front-End Developer transitioning into IT after many years of working in education. My teaching experience has equipped me with strong analytical skills, problem-solving abilities, and teamwork capabilities. With a foundation in JavaScript, React and HTML/CSS, I focus on crafting functional, visually appealing web applications to enhance user experiences.

Proposals for cooperation with technologies that need to be studied are welcome!

CONTACT DETAILS

irvna.skaraieva@gmail.com

62 +421919495444

Trnava, Slovak Republic

LINKS TO OTHER RESOURSES

Portfolio **WhatsApp Telegram**

Facebook GitHub Linkedin

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

SCSS

React

Next.is

Figma

Bulma

Tailwind CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Manager

Freelance, Vinnytsya, UA | Feb 2016 - May 2017

- · Researched and edited photos and product descriptions to optimize content for online stores.
- · Managed content updates, gaining experience in web content structuring and user experience.

Teacher of Physics and Astronomy

Medical College, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2014 - Aug 2015 Secondary School, Odesa, UA | Sep 2007 - Sep 2012

- · Created educational materials (presentations, interactive content), building skills in design and multimedia.
- · Managed large amounts of information, developed instructional documentation.

· Processed financial transactions and records, requiring data

· Handled large datasets for reporting, building analytical

· Adapted to new software, showing flexibility and a quick

· Supervised student groups.

accuracy and attention to detail.

learning curve for new tools.

Accountant

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian C2

C2

Enalish B1

EDUCATION

В

DRIVING LICENSE

The Faculty of Physics and Mathematics

Teacher of Physics, Computer Science and Life Safety Basics

Master's degree Sep 2002 — June 2007

T&T, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2013 - Mar 2013

thinking relevant in software development.

South Ukrainian National Pedagogical University named after K. D. Ushynsky

Russian

Slovak R1